<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maximizing Value of Data</title>
    <link>http://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Maximizing Value of Data</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-FR</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2015</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>The key to successful online marketing is to deliver the most relevant and engaging content to your audience. And this is what we, at IntentAware™, excel at. IntentAware™ is a cloud based Data Management Platform (DMP) that is bridging the gap between your digital content and relevant audience. Through sophisticated real time data analysis, our proprietary decision engine recognizes people’s intent and enables marketers, agencies, and publishers to reach end-users in their intent path when they are most likely to be influenced and make purchase decisions - enhancing customer engagement and conversion rate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Actionable Data</title>
      <link>http://example.com/post/actionabledata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/post/actionabledata/</guid>
      <description>We capture user data from any device, across multiple locations, and from multiple devices. Our proprietary technology performs real time analysis of content, user context, and user data, including 1st and 3rd party data. We analyze the behavior of over 500 million Internet users, detect their locations and devices, and deduces their interest and intent, among others data points - a 360-degree view of your online users. We do not rely on 3rd party cookies and our solution is mobile optimized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Direct Mail to the Digital Age</title>
      <link>http://example.com/casestudies/direct-mail-in-digital-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/casestudies/direct-mail-in-digital-age/</guid>
      <description>Background: In the lead up to the holiday season of 2015, John a retailer of luxury jewelry items was wondering what he could do differently to increase sales in a cost efficient manner. He had tried the traditional routes of Google AdWords, flyers etc. but he was not able to get the word out to a net new audience.
Fortunately, at a professional networking event, John met Arvind Singh the founder of www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://example.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/contact/</guid>
      <description> Your Name:  Your Email  Message   Send  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IntentAware for Auto Industry</title>
      <link>http://example.com/casestudies/autoindustry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/casestudies/autoindustry/</guid>
      <description>Research1 shows that more than 72% of auto buyers use the Internet for research and comparison activities before purchasing. As a result, Internet houses a lot of intent data of these prospects as potential buyers navigate across different auto websites. Until now, as an auto brand or dealer, you don’t have this real time prospect insights i.e., who is visiting your website, comparing vehicles, etc.
 IntentAware™ is meeting this need and adding value to Auto Industry through real time actionable online customer intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IntentAware for Banking Industry</title>
      <link>http://example.com/casestudies/banking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/casestudies/banking/</guid>
      <description>Ad spending on paid digital media by the US financial services was about &amp;amp;7.2 billion in 2015 – a gain of 14.5% over 2014 and the trend continues for at least next five years with a CAGR of 11.7%1 (eMarketer, September 2015). But what about returns on this astronomical investment? A dismal 0.003%! Clearly, something is missing. And the most obvious is random targeting – these are the people who don’t care about your product or are not in the market yet advertisers keep investing on random targeting in the hope to sell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ip Intelligence</title>
      <link>http://example.com/post/ipintelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/post/ipintelligence/</guid>
      <description>Our proprietary technology provides you insight on your online customers – know from where and how they are connecting to web. This information can further be used to curb online fraud and mitigate compliance risks related to online sales. Best of all, you can get this information within seconds (~18 seconds) to either boost your customer engagement or prevent fraud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lead Intelligence</title>
      <link>http://example.com/post/leadintelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/post/leadintelligence/</guid>
      <description>Understanding your customer is key to engaging them and run effective campaigns. What if you could shorten your sales cycles and deliver relevant offers to prospects? Gain a clear picture of your prospects - who are they, what influences them, their interests &amp;amp; lifestyle profile - a ‘must-have’ intelligence to foster product, service and feature innovation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sample Case Study for Retail</title>
      <link>http://example.com/casestudies/retail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/casestudies/retail/</guid>
      <description>Our team conducted an experiment workshop where we told shoppers to buy things from giant retailers in canada. The experience of the online buyers was tedious , time consuming and going thorough multiple pages. Also in the end the consumer journey is broken due to an offline journey like a flyer.
Our Marketing solution can provide bliss to online consumers by uniting thier intent and online journey in just 3 clicks</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>